[Music]
[Música]
What's up, did you see a fish or not? Let's watch the
qué pasa se te vio un pez o no a ver el
live broadcast of Tele Salsero. Let me explain.
directo de tele salsero lo explico
Well, what was seen in the
bueno lo que se habían visto en los
earnings, basically I switched screens
ingresos básicamente cambie de pantalla
and had to open the studio. Open the
y tenía abrir el estudio abrir el
YouTube studio. I wanted to show it. I wanted to
youtube estudio quería mostrar quería
explain to people so that they knew how to
explicarle a la gente para que se como
see who was subscribed to your
se podía ver quién estaba suscrito a tu
channel and who wasn't. That it's not possible, you don't
canal y quién no que no se puede no se
have enough audiences. No,
tenga suficiente públicas no
and then I had the YouTube
y entonces tenía abierto en youtube
studio open and they saw my earnings for about
estudio y se vieron mis ingresos durante
half a second. Okay, but I'm
un medio segundo vale pero lo estoy
cutting it for a month and I can remove it, so
recortando mes y lo puedo quitar por lo
if more Villa supports this,
que si más villa apoya está se vieron
the bills were seen. They gave me the bills,
los billetes se me dieron los billetes
the five euro bills. I didn't
los billetes de cinco euros no se me
get the 300 euros to earn. Your
dieron los 300 euros que ganarme tu
beard is coming back. You see,
barba está regresando tú ves también no
nothing's happening. I shave it. You want me to
pasa nada me la rasuró queréis que me la
trash it again live. I've
basura otra vez en directo yo me ha
resolved myself. The fact is, I uploaded the video to the
resuelto el hecho es subió vídeo al
main channel. Okay,
canal principal vale
the main channel. Right now, we're
el canal principal ya mismo le vamos a
going to put a stone on it and we're going to
le vamos a poner la lápida y lo vamos a
leave it. And it won't leave the main channel
dejar y ya no sale del canal principal
anymore. We have to accept it. No,
ya debemos de asumirlo no
I think the sooner we accept it, the
yo creo que cuanto antes lo asumamos
better. But anyway, what's happening here is
mejor pero bueno yo lo de aquí
Oliveira. He
oliveira
uploaded the video.  on the main channel the
el subió vídeo en el canal principal la
person who wanted to destroy Chozas's career
persona que quiso destruir la carrera
you are going to change studies javi and
te vas a cambiar de estudios javi y
very soon very soon I don't know if it's roasted they are
prontísimo prontísimo no sé si sea asado
going because Mr. Hería's videos
van porque los vídeos del señor hería se
keep getting visited although
mantienen en visitas aunque igual los
Mr. Erías's videos keep getting
vídeos de señor erías se mantienen en
visited because Mrs. Hería gets
visitas porque la señor hería
tired of sharing them on Facebook
se harta de compartirlos en facebook
especially they don't stop sharing the
sobre todo no paran de compartir los
videos although although I have a video they
vídeos aunque aunque el vídeo tengo un
keep sharing it it's worth it whether it's the
me siguen compartiendo lo vale sea los
videos of the Lordship the first the
vídeos de la señoría la primera el
first day it happens to them the same as everyone else they
primer día les pasa igual que a todos
have 15 thousand visits 20 thousand visits what
tienen 15 mil visitas 20 mil visitas lo
happens is that then they get tired of
que pasa es que luego se hartan de
sharing it on Facebook they only share it
compartirlo en facebook sólo comparten
on WhatsApp and in the end they all pass
por whatsapp y al final pues todos pasan
100,000 look at this video for
las 100.000 mira este video desde hace
three weeks it had 30 or 40
tres semanas estaba tenía 30 o 40
visits writing right now 10 100
visitas escribiendo ahora mismo 10 100
thousand the good one the same thing I'll leave the
mil el de bueno lo mismo lo dejo el
channel for only videos of Lordships I do
canal para solo vídeos de señorías
n't know
no sé
the safest thing is that no the safest thing is that I will
lo más seguro es que no lo más seguro es
continue working and making videos of
que siga trabajando y haciendo videos de
everyone and those that have few visits by
todos y los que tengan pocas visitas por
time to visits are
tiempo a visitas estás
I imagine that depending on the subject
me imagino que dependiendo del tema
will continue to rise  no but it's not normal it
seguirá levantando no pero no es normal
's not normal at all this video of
no es normal ni de coña este vídeo de
ibai with this piece of thumbnail hahaha
ibai con esta pedazo de miniatura jajaja
but well, they are timeless videos
pero bueno yo son vídeos atemporales
well well I wouldn't know what to say or rather
bueno bueno no sabría qué decir o sea
temporary I wouldn't know but look at the
temporal eso no lo sabría pero mirá la
interview with fran it wasn't bad 100 thousand
entrevista con fran no fue mal 100 mil
visits already also almost well I keep
visitas ya también casi bueno yo sigo
creating in the end in the month there are one million
creando al final en el mes son un millón
200 thousand visits a million and a half
200 mil visitas un millón y medio
the main channel well if this work
el canal principal pues si este trabajo
and this time invested is only
y este tiempo invertido solamente lo
appreciated by the ladies and the kids don't
aprecian las señoras y los chavales no
appreciate it and they don't share it, they don't give it a
lo aprecian y no lo comparten no le dan
line, they don't comment on those things, then the
line no comentan en esas cosas pues el
main channel will remain only
canal principal se quedará únicamente
for what I feel like uploading like
para lo que me apetezca a subir
[Music]
[Música]
or functions, we'll see, we'll see for
o funciones ya veremos ya veremos de
now for a few months I'm going to keep
momento durante unos meses voy a seguir
trying, continuing to upload what I do, it's that they have
probando siguiendo subiendo lo que hago
few, they have few what
ya está que tienen pocas tienen pocas lo
matters are the final visits of the
que importa son las visitas finales del
month and in the end it is at the end of the month the month ends
mes y al final es al mes se acaba el mes
with one and a half million visits
con un millón y medio de visitas
visits well it's still old it's still
visitas pues todavía edad todavía
profitable
todavía sale rentable
even chili is adding variety
hasta el chile está metiendo variedad
you have videos each main one so you
tenéis vídeos cada principal para que lo
know what you're putting in
sepáis que estás metiendo
now
ahora
and always  The same thing happens to him
y siempre le pasa igual
in the south it happens to him because he has had a
por el sur le pasa porque tiene el canal
very abandoned channel
muy abandonado
for a long time, I
de hace tiempo
mean, he hadn't uploaded videos for two months
o sea llevaba dos meses sin subir vídeos
and the previous 30 thousand
y no le iban mal los anteriores 30 mil
22 thousand twenty-something were doing well, which was good,
22 mil veintitantos que estaba bueno
good for half the subscribers but
bien para la mitad de suscriptores pero
today they invited the chura, the
que hoy han invitado al chura lo del
tweet
tweet
[Music]
[Música]
the sweater if I can say it yes no
el jersey si lo puedo decir sí no
well I don't know
bueno no lo sé
there's another event where they burn
hay otro evento en el que queman
guests but I don't know if they will invite
invitados pero no sé si habrán invitar
the south it was to ask him why
al sur era para preguntarle por qué
well I'll say it when I can say it if I find out that they
bueno ya lo digo cuando pueda decirlo si
invite him I'll say it okay let's
me entero que le invitan lo digo vale a
see nothing coming every main okay okay okay let's
ver que nada que viene cada principal
see if you have a way again
a ver si tienes de manera de nuevo
now not tomorrow
ahora no de mañana
listen to me
escúchame
the abandoned sweaters I forgot
le abandonado del suéteres se me olvide
but the ball
pero la bola
the ridiculous that we're going to feel soon you'll
el ridículo que vamos a sentir pronto ya
see well let's see you told me
lo veréis bueno a ver me habéis dicho
that aurum play has literally destroyed
que aurum play ha destrozado
literally destroyed willy rex for
destrozado literalmente a willy rex por
the nfts let's see let's
los nfts vamos a ver
see try try try try try try try try eye
vamos a ver
eye the coolest game no what
ojo ojo que el juego más chulo no que
game this so
juego este
eye so handsome this fact this
así que ojo tanto guapo este hecho este
game no  so because of you the
juego no así que por tu culpa la tarjeta
graphics card found me double okay
gráfica me encontró el doble vale no
nothing happens I'll just go bust the
pasa nada sólo iré a reventar del
business clown I love you Carlos because of you
negocio payaso te quiero carlos por tu
the graphics card cost me
culpa en la tarjeta gráfica me costó el
double right nothing happens I'll just go
doble correcto no pasa nada sólo iré a
bust your business
reventar te el negocio
mister questions it seems like a chip in an
mister questions parece chip en un
internet cafe simulator to you handsome
simulador del ciber café a vuestra guapo
this but that anecdote
este pero esa anécdota
really the graphics cards are not there because of
realmente las tarjetas gráficas no hay
these things among other
por culpa de estas cosas entre otras
things
cosas
I have investments in Christ coins
yo tengo inversiones en cristos monedas
call you the fabric
llamarte la tela
and I have no [ __ ] idea why
y no tengo ni [__] idea de por qué tiene
graphics cards have to do with
que ver las tarjetas gráficas con las
Christ ways I still swear
cristo maneras todavía os lo juro
Sanz I have no [ __ ] idea why what
sanz no tengo ni [__] idea de por qué de
graphics cards and mining have to do with each other I mean I don't understand
gráficas y minar o sea que no entiendo
use graphics cards are to
usa las tarjetas gráficas son para
put them in the computer so that the
ponerlas en el ordenador para que el
computer runs video games better
ordenador te corra mejor los videojuegos
to put look at the fish and to mine
para poner a mirar el peces y para minar
what does it mean to
qué significa
finish what does it mean
terminar qué significa
but to look that is I don't understand what to look is I mean
pero mirar que es que no entiendo lo que
the 5th way is not like the stock market they are
la 5° manera no es como la bolsa son son
companies they are companies they are securities and today they are
empresas son empresas son valores y hoy
worth one dollar and tomorrow they are worth two
valen un dólar y mañana valen dos
dollars or so  lower and they're worth half a
dólares oa lo más baja y valen medio
dollar don't create christ coin but what does it
dólar no crear cristo moneda pero que me
give me really I don't understand
da de verdad no lo entiendo
in a
en una
big cage javi I've followed you since the
jaula grande javi te sigo desde los
beginning and I've never had the chance to
inicios y nunca he tenido la oportunidad
thank you for all the
de agradecer que todos los ratos de
fun times you've offered me
diversión que me has ofrecido muchas
thank you very much king for the office a
gracias a ti rey por el ofi un abrazo
huge hug let's go to Paula's and let's
enorme vamos a de paula y vamos a
clear one thing up because today I took a
aclarar una cosa porque hoy cogido
screenshot of the conversation we
captura de pantalla de la conversación
had okay here you have
que hemos tenido vale ya aquí tenéis la
my conversation with Paula this afternoon I
conversación mía con paula de esta tarde
call her at 7:35
le hablo a las 19
19:35 I put Paulo you're
1935 le pongo paulo estás
at
a las
I see that she doesn't answer me right when she
veo que no me responde al momento cuando
has to answer us and I put the
me tiene que respondernos y le pongo el
cell phone in her hand like cucha cucha
móvil de la manita en plan cucha cucha
father
padre
and there she answers at 8:11
y ahí me responde a las 8 y 11
and says yes tell me and I tell her it was a test it
y dice si dime y le digo era una prueba
took half an hour she
tarda media hora
puts the [ __ ] 'we and the [ __ ] frog' on me
me pone el [__] 'hemos y de la rana de
and tells me I was asleep and I
[__] y me dice estaba dormido y le
tell her next time do you think about the two
digo la próxima vez piensas de los dos
times how good that you want to charge
veces que bien que quieres cobrar
now come again to piss me off
ahora venir otra vez a tocarme los
too much that they have a
[__] demasiado que tienen un canal de
shitty channel for  the fact that they charge
[__] por el que cobran
too much
demasiado
too much seems
demasiado me parece
like a joke to me but that anecdote
parece chiste pero esa anécdota
there are problems with the supply of
hay problemas de abastecimiento de
graphics cards because of this yes
tarjetas gráficas por culpa de esto
yes
sí sí
as you hear it
como lo oye
incredible the issue of mining and all
increíble el tema de la minería y todo
that I do not understand anything about that
eso yo es que no entiendo nada de ese
world the truth is I understand it
mundo la verdad yo lo entiende una
[ __ ] is that I do not understand what they
[__] es que no entiendo que lo que
have to do graphics card with the
tienen que hacer tarjeta gráfica con la
Egyptian currency like that he swear mining
egipto moneda así él lo juro la minería
in this way is the process in which
de dicha manera es el proceso en el que
miners use
los mineros utilizan la potencia
computing power to process transactions
informática para procesar transacciones
and obtain rewards in this case of
y obtener recompensa en este caso de
this currency said another way is the
esta moneda dicho de otra forma es el
process of adding a new
proceso de agregar un nuevo registro de
transaction record like blocking or also
transacciones como bloquear o también
what example but I do not understand
que ejemplo pero es que no entiendo una
[ __ ] what more explained I do not understand I do
[__] lo que más explicado no entiendo
not see the relationship but well it
no le veo la relación pero bueno alguna
has some and I do not give a damn no I do not
tiene y me importa tres huevos
understand anything about that world either I do not
no no entiendo nada de ese mundo tampoco
need it the truth
lo necesito la verdad
what
qué
is here for what I
está aquí para qué
understand that there are people who want to
entiendo que haya gente que quiera
undertake and this alba I do not understand
emprender y está alba no lo entiendo
but people who already have money here here
pero gente que ya tiene pasta aquí aquí
if you already have money or shut up
si ya tienes dinero o cállate
because you are going to get into that that will
porque te vas a meter en eso que te va a
give you a million more wow you are not going to notice
dar un millón más wow no vas a notar
much the difference of having  10 million
mucho la diferencia de tener 10 millones
to have 11
a tener 11
the truth is that I don't understand it I don't
la verdad es que no lo entiendo no lo
understand it I understand entrepreneurial people
entiendo yo entiendo a gente
mind you
ojo
I thought about it too there are a lot of people who
yo también lo pensé hay mucha gente que
can say that willy needs to
se puede decir que willy requiere
scam that he wants to deceive his
estafar que quiere engañar a sus
followers to win I opened up it's like
seguidores para ganar me abrí es como
seeing if willy has to be a clod he has to find
ver si willy tiene que estar terrón
willy's bank account
willy
I already have to be making videos and
yo ya tiene que estar haciendo vídeos y
direct pana
directo pana
for nothing completely and now
para para nada completamente y ahora
this is done with
esto se lo hace de
this nfc thing
esto de los nfc
I think he's doing it because I don't
yo creo que lo está haciendo porque no
know for fun because it draws attention
sé por gusto porque llama la atención
because he knows everyone will get nfc finally we'll
porque sabe todos sacarán nfc finalmente
see when the market for
ya se verá cuando crezca el mercado de
this grows well the issue of effects another
esto pues el tema de los efectos otra
thing I don't understand a [ __ ] because there is
cosa no entiendo una [__] porque es
everything there are 800 people
que hay todo hay 800 las personas
selling drawings they are all
vendiendo dibujitos son todos los
drawings with the same pose more or
dibujitos con la misma postura más o
less a doll
menos un muñeco
a drawing of super tacky drawings
un dibujo de dibujos súper cutres
normally
normalmente
super tacky drawings that change the
dibujos super cutres que le cambian de
color from one to the other the glasses are some have a
uno al otro el color las gafas son unos
pattern another the goat you know how but I don't
un patrón otro la cabra sabes cómo
get into them either because
pero tampoco me meto con ellos porque
I think it will be the typical thing that
pienso que será la típica cosa que hoy
criticizes everyone today and within  7
critica a todo el mundo y dentro de 7
years we will all do on our channels
años todos haremos en nuestros canales
I understand then how the 21st happened and
me entiendo entonces como pasaba el 21 y
also normally here in strange we are
además normalmente aquí en extrañas
always years behind the
siempre vamos con años de retraso al
rest of the countries maybe in this country
resto de países a lo mejor en este país
they are making a lot of youtubers
están haciendo un montón de youtubers
and here we will do it
y aquí lo haremos
when people started to donate
cuando la gente empezó a las donaciones
the petril I don't know what
el petril no sé qué sabe
people know who want to try and hey want to
gente que quiere probar y oye quiere
get ahead as they can but people who
salir adelante como pueda pero gente que
already have money so you get into this
ya tiene pasta para que te metes en esto
the truth is I wouldn't get into it sincerely
la verdad yo no me metería sinceramente
I wouldn't get into it and look that they have offered it to me they have
yo no me metería y mira que me lo han
sent me many emails
ofrecido me han enviado muchos emails
many have sent me many emails of
muchos me han enviado muchos emails de
nfc from me I read it I already have enough I
nfc de mí me lo leo ya tengo bastante ya
am already well damn
estoy bien [__]
the classroom has to be really cool also
el aula tiene que está padrísimo también
in bills but at the level of millions and
en billetes pero a nivel millones y
millions of euros
millones de euros
'come on millions and millions of euros to
'vamos millones y millones de euros para
not work anymore surely what I
no trabajar más seguro segurísimo lo que
do I already do it for pleasure for
haga ya lo hace por gusto por placer por
personal goals and such and be a
metas personales y tales y estar a unos
few years with this of the tweets
cuantos de años con esto del tweets
until that art and it will be I am going is that I
hasta que ese arte y ya será voy es que
already tell you be since for that already the
ya te digo sea ya que para que ya el
money that he has for that you know
dinero que tiene para que sabes
the truth
la verdad
but yes yes now it is very strong and
pero sí sí ahora está eso muy fuerte y
many companies  they have offered it like I don't even
muchas empresas me lo han ofrecido como
understand it of course I said I don't understand it
ni lo entiendo claro dije no lo entiendo
either that's why I understand it
tampoco por eso lo entiendo
and I'm not just saying it for Willy and I say it in
y no lo digo sólo por willy y lo digo en
general I don't understand like also
general no entiendo como también
elite athletes and
deportistas de élite y deportistas de
elite athletes neymar neymar who sells celeste I don't
élite neymar neymar que vende celeste no
understand if the millionaire
entiendo si el millonario
neymar if it's like the fashion I do to
neymar si es como la moda hago para
act like a cool guy you know the video is
hacerse el chulo sabéis el vídeo es el
from Patricia's diary to act like a cool guy
del diario de patricia para hacerse el
in which you smoke
en el que fumas
to be cooler but well as soon as you
para ser más chulo pero bueno en cuanto
foam
espumas
a package of passes
un paquete de pases
that later came out in the present not
que luego salió en la actualidad no
current
actualidad
and he is
y él
in the past it
en el pasado
's the
es el
third video let's see which one this is the
el tercer vídeo a ver cuál éste es el
[Music]
[Música]
it's the one in reality it
es el en realidad
looks it looks horrible I
se ve se ve horrible
already said it for athletes there are many
ya lo digo por deportistas hay muchos
who have taken out NFC
que han sacado nfc
and earn 10 million a year 15 that you take out
y cobran 10 millones al año 15 que sacas
that [ __ ]
esa [__]
that I don't understand why
que no entiendo por qué
but well hey I don't know maybe if I
pero bueno oye no sé quizás si lo
understood it more this world would win me
entendiera más este mundillo me ganaría
more times I don't understand it it's that I like
más veces no lo entiendo es que me gusta
the world I have always been it's
el mundo siempre he estado
not that I understand it one hundred percent and I
no es que lo entienda al cien por cien y
am a great and labor tino well  it's
sea un gran y laborales tino pues es
simple I'm interested in the stock market when you
simple me interesa la bolsa cuando
get these coins because they had
logras que estos monedas pues tenían
money to invest I invested it in something
dinero para invertir lo invertí en algo
more or less the ones that the most in those that
más o menos las que más en las que
appeared more reliable I understand
aparecían más confiables me entiende
optimal responded the south but hello hello
óptima respondió el sur pero hola hola
hello
hola
your body next to mine because my soul
tu cuerpo junto al mío porque mi alma no
has no time does the name or title exist
tiene tiempo existe el nombre o título
Paula you have a new
paula tienes una nueva misión de
training mission you know
entrenamiento lo sabes
I know what it is to buy something to later
yo sé que es comprar algo para luego
sell it for more expensive it's the summary talking
venderlo más caro es el resumen hablando
talking for the live television to the pse
hablando para el directo de teles al pse
or in a little while and he treated her badly not
o en un ratito y la trató mal no
speaking badly and quickly I think it's
hablando mal y rápido creo que es
buying something for a price to later be
comprar algo por un precio para luego
able to sell it for more expensive yes yes yes
poder venderlo más caro sí sí sí
literally that but Sergio let's see there are
literalmente eso pero sergio a ver hay
so many drawings that are sold
tantísimos dibujos que se venden quien
whoever wants is going to buy your drawing I just
quien quiere va a comprar tu dibujo es
don't understand right
que no entiendo verdad
the jealousy of a [ __ ] [ __ ] those of the
los celos de una [__] [__] los de los
ft but well let's see what
el ft pero bueno vamos a ver qué
possibilities there are with that I do
posibilidades hay con eso
n't know what possibility of doing with that
no sé qué posibilidad de hacer con eso
so we will see with the passage of
así que lo iremos viendo con el paso del
time but right now I don't understand the
tiempo pero ahora mismo no entiendo la
[ __ ] willy said no it's that this opens
[__] willy dijo no es que esto te abre
a path of infinite possibilities I don't
un camino de posibilidades infinitas no
know what it is like watts of a lifetime
sé qué es como watts de toda la vida
like the stock market  I could say a little bit,
como la bolsa se podría decir un poquito
no, yes, of course, like the bag of I see the
no sí claro como la bolsa de yo veo la
writing on the currency like the bags,
escrito la moneda como las bolsas
then in my day, well, I was
entonces yo en su día pues me estuvo
informing myself by reading a lot of things and
informando leyendo un montón de cosas e
informing myself that neither that I am the
informando que tampoco que yo sea la
other one who understood of understanding each
otra que comprendió de comprender cada
writing currency of what is behind
escrito moneda de lo que hay detrás
simply well
simplemente pues
also in August very good people are exhibited, I
también en agosto se exhiba gente muy
follow very good people
buena sigo a gente muy buena
know so well that's where it went for me, let's
sabe entonces pues por ahí me fue vamos
do where to invest until
a hacer de donde donde invertir hasta el
today at least I got it right and it has
día de hoy por lo menos lo acerté y me
gone very well for me with the Christ which is a
ha ido muy bien con las cristo que es un
world that I do not recommend you
mundo del que yo no os recomiendo
get into people unless you test that they
meterse a la gente a no ser que test que
have money that you know you are not going to
tengan un dinero que sepas que no lo vas
need in your entire life and that you can
a necesitar en toda la vida y que puedes
assume to lose it, in other words, that it stays at
asumir perderlo o sea que se quede el
zero that you are going to lose it and you do not care,
cero que lo vas a perder y te da igual
okay,
vale
a lot of people who have,
un montón de gente que tiene
have NFC, even Justin Bieber has brought them
tiene nfc hasta justin bieber los ha
out
sacado
as fashionable now, they do not mean anything to me
como de moda ahora a mí no me dicen nada
in my opinion, the same in two years it is
en mi opinión igual de aquí dos años es
the future, hey, for who knows the truth,
el futuro oye por quién sabe la verdad
of course,
claro
a man and he gave it to him and the other day a
a un hombre y le dio la y el otro día un
tweet from Windmill, his uncle, trust you that  they were
tweet de windmill su tío fide tu que se
supposed to be terrible
suponía que estaban fatal
and in fact with michu he has put some
y de hecho with michu le ha puesto unas
bids now very low for my taste and
pujas ahora muy bajas para mi gusto y
some blows very low for my taste and
unos golpes muy bajos para mi gusto y
however laurel gave him the hague a
sin embargo laurel le dio la haya un
tweet from wish michu that win michu is going all
tweet de wish michu que win michu va a
out for willy you know win michu I think
saco por willy sabe win michu yo creo
that if he was already hungry for willy since
que si ya le tenía hambre a willy desde
willy spoke out against win
que willy se pronunció en contra de win
michu for the Andorra issue the Dallas issue
michu por el tema andorra el tema dallas
and so on he accused him macho there was and
y demás le lo acusó a macho había y
both win michu and how will I become good I will become maybe he
tanto win michu como como me haré bueno
gives it to him it has been
me haré a lo mejor le da la haya sido
very much but above all guys michu is going all
muy mucho pero sobre todo guys michu va
out retweeting putting things
a saco retuiteando poniendo cosas en
against willy a lot and the other day
contra de willy a saco y el otro día
well owen mich a tweet that he sends all this to me
pues owen mich un tuit que todo esto me
and today something that is very saved
lo manda y hoy cosa que la muy guardado
well in case I make a video whatever and
bueno por si hago vídeo lo que sea y
about wii assuming things from willy he
de wii suponiendo cosas de willy me
sends me since at that moment and it was a tweet that
manda ya que momento y era un tweet que
said something like that I was thinking shut up
decía algo así que pensaba que te calles
already heavy and willy gave one like
ya pesado y willy a uno le daba like
who knows how [ __ ] I understand that you don't
quién sabe cómo [__] entiendo que no
want war but
quieres guerra pero
you are a little more discreet depends on
me eres un poco más discreta depende con
what  the subject depends on what subject it is, lately I
qué tema depende con qué tema yo
see them again looking for, I don't know
los veo otra vez a saco buscando no sé
if controversy or to talk about it or whatever,
si polémicas o que se hable o lo que sea
at first it wasn't my place but I see what
yo en un principio no era pero veo qué
[Music]
[Música]
to comment on, I
para comentar lo
reported it in May, I don't care, take out your
denuncié en mayo no me importa a sacarte
videos, right? Don't report me anymore,
los vídeos verdad no me denuncien más el
metal in the future Javi, I don't know, I won't
metal en el futuro javi no sé yo tampoco
find you either. I haven't said that I'm
te encontraré no he dicho que esté en
against it, I said that at the moment I'm not
contra he dicho que yo de momento no me
interested in [ __ ], but just like I'm
interesa la [__] pero igual que te
telling you right now I'm not interested in
digo ahora mismo no me interesa una
[ __ ], maybe in two years he'll
[__] a lo mejor dentro de dos años le
get the hang of it, I see the possibility that
pilló el rollo veo la posibilidad de que
something useful can be done and I say I
se pueda hacer algo útil y digo me
love it, you know, I don't close the doors, he doesn't
encanta sabes no cierro las puertas no
close the door, okay, I think that
cierra la puerta vale pienso que la
people who get into that stuff have to
gente que se meta en esas cosas tienen
do it super well advised, super
que hacerlo súper bien asesorados súper
well, you know what I'm telling you, man,
bien sabe lo que te digo hombre ese
seen the palace he's doing around here and
visto el palacio que hace por aquí y
dude you don't sleep or what today I
churra no duermes o que hoy precisamente
saw a video of yours Victor
vi un vídeo tuyo víctor
was eating, I was putting my video
estaba comiendo estaba poniendo mi vídeo
here rando and I saw the video saying
aquí rando y vi el vídeo decir
why it was, thank you very much
porque era muchas gracias
and the video of Ciro's video
y el video de sido de el vídeo de ciro
that Julia replaced him in the
que julia le sustituyó en el juego del
squid game, the other one  day and I videoed it bands
calamar el otro día y me lo vídeo bandas
like I had how I ran into her in the
como tuve como me crucé con ella en el
video
vídeo
and after that I saw a video of yours
y después de ese me salió un vídeo tuyo
of the fight between Ciro and Josep Pedrerol and
de la pelea de ciro con josep pedrerol y
I was watching a video a
te estuve viendo un vídeo un vídeo
powerful video that made me almost half a million
potente que te haga yo casi medio millón
visits was that I said watch the video
de visitas era que dije mirá el video
with that shitty hair
con ese pelo de [__]
words smile thank you very much for
palabras sonreír muchas gracias por
stopping by subscribe everyone to Victor
pasarte suscribiros todos a víctor
Palacios if you don't know him and if you like
palacios si no lo conocéis y si os gusta
sports world you already know that this is
el deporte mundo ya sabéis que esto es
like the ones they buy dolls today the big
como los que compran los muñecos hoy los
headed dolls how ugly it is true it is a
muñecos cabezones qué feo verdad es un
flake I have a couple of a flake here
copo yo tengo aquí un par de un copo
but since I am literally 21
pero como literalmente tengo 21
one that I think was given to me by a girl
uno que creo que me lo regaló una tía
who then started slandering me all over
que luego me estuvo difamando por toda
the girl because the girl was
la tipa porque la tipa fue
a girl who really wanted
era una tía que quería por [__] a
six of my friends from Lorena but as if she
seis amigos míos de lorena pero en plan
went around saying that she was
que iba por ahí diciendo que tenía
friends with us and that
amistad con nosotros y que convienen
our house is good for us and the whole thing a move
nuestra casa y todo el rollo una movida
dude that's why over the years I have
tío por eso yo a lo largo de los años he
learned that the less you talk
ido aprendiendo que cuanto menos hables
to the people who write you messages m  I
con la gente que te escribe mensah m o
mean, I don't talk to anyone, the contexts,
sea yo no hablo con nadie los contextos
the messages here in the live streams when
los mensajes aquí en los directos cuando
I say let's listen, draw, send me,
digo vamos a escuchar dibujen me mandan
let's do it, but I go into private messages
vamos a hacer pero mensajes privados me
to see what you're sending me, like
meto para ver lo que me estáis mandando
this, for example, she sent me to
en plan esto por ejemplo me ha mandado a
the garden or sometimes she demands things,
la huerta o algunas veces demanda cosas
those of you who send things, I look at your dm's
los que mandáis cosas yo os miro los md
but I don't talk, okay, because it's the day,
pero yo no hablo vale porque es el día
then she was informing me, I'm about to
luego fue informando me apunto de
sue, she'll pass it on after serving, I'm
demandar la pasará después de servir a
going to sue her and Santi is going to
la voy a demandar y santi a se va a
get a public defender and he's not going to have to
pillar un abogado de oficio y no va a
pay because obviously he
tener para pagar porque evidente que se
continues to be a pain in the ass one day but it already
sigue dando por culo algún día pero ya
fell but she posted information it was
se cayó pero puso de informaciones fue
yesterday she posted cold information because I
ayer puso informaciones frías porque
had here at the time she stayed with Lorena
tuve aquí en su momento quedó por lorena
or because Lorena I do
o porque lorena
n't remember how but she stayed with Lorena,
no me acuerdo cómo pero quedó con lorena
people who
personas que
worked at a place that was on the way,
trabajaban un sitio que venía de camino
come on, okay, if you want
venga vale si quieren
the stitch, okay, and pay her later, well, I
el stich vale y la paga luego pues me
found out that she was saying that she should eat at
enteré que iba diciendo que comiera
our house and that I had told her I
nuestra casa y que yo le había contado
don't know how many but intimate things that I say,
no sé cuántas pero intimidades que digo
my mother for God's sake
yo madre mía por dios
and the aunt was saying  that she was a
y la tía iba diciendo que era amiga
close friend of ours so I don't know who
nuestra por [__] entonces no sé quién
asked me on md what her friend followed up with
me preguntó por md que siguió la amiga
so I answered I haven't
de ella pues le contesté yo no la he
seen her a couple of times and good people I don't
visto un par de veces y buena gente no
know what and when she found out that I
sé qué y cuando se enteró de que yo
had denied that she was my friend she got
había negado que era mi amiga pues se
angry and started informing me everywhere
rebotó y empezó a informarme por todos
but now I know that's why she didn't report me
pero ya sé que por eso no la denuncia
the certified tubes they have them and
los tubos certificados los tienen y
then I have another one it was a flake that I don't know what
luego tengo otro fue un copo que no sé
the Jack Skellington one
que el de jack esqueleto que me lo ha
my sister denied it to me and then the only one that
negado mi hermana y luego el único que
I buy
yo me compra
the only one that I would buy
el único que yo me compraba fue este
was this one because I loved it and then the doll made I don't think my daughter would buy it in a stuffing something that is also cool but it's very rare it's very rare that I like it in a football to spare they became very fashionable in their time but
se pusieron muy de moda en su época pero
and the
y la
island
isla
[Music]
[Música]
the truth is a nice collection of figures the one
la verdad colección guapa de figuras la
I have from Disney Infinity look for it
que yo tengo de disney infinity buscarlo
look for Disney Infinity figures but
buscar figuras de disney infinity pero
if you want to see the wave wait a moment already they are
si queréis ver la ola un momento
no longer on the market in
ya vaya ya no están en el mercado de
fact the figure let's never
hecho la figura vamos nunca la voy a
sell it in my life in the  price of mercy
vender en la vida en el precio de piedad
I have already seen that there are some for
yo he visto ya que hay algunas por las
which they ask for a thousand euros the figures are
que piden mil euros a las figuras son la
literally the best look at
[__] literales mira
the figures are the best I would have to
las figuras son la [__]
see them up close ok like
la tendría que ver de cerca vale en plan
the design that has the face
el diseño que tiene la cara a la
perfectly knows all the
perfección sabe de todas las películas
marvel star war movies I have
de marvel star war las tengo
absolutely all of them I think I didn't miss a single
absolutamente todas creo que no me faltó
one I think I don't know
ni una creo no lo sé
and the figure are pretty pretty I don't
y la figura son guapa guapa esta no la
have this one I think it
tengo creo
could have been saved from what
que podría haber salvado de que nos
came out in the end I do
salieron al final
n't know why it wasn't successful because let's see
no sé por qué no tuvo éxito porque a ver
the truth the figure will be it is that they were
la verdad la figura será es que eran
figures that cost a lot
figuras que costaban mucho
for the nonsense of the game would have been because
para la tontería de juego hubiera porque
the game was a game for
el juego era un juego para niños
very small children ok but now the figures
pequeñísimos vale pero ahora las figuras
were high quality back then they cost 20
eran de alta calidad entonces costaba 20
or 30 euros figures
o 30 euros figuras
sulistyo current very cool to give some
sulistyo actualísima chulísima dar unos
details and a style xavi to a
detalles y un estilo xavi a un estilo
super super cool style they give a thousand turns to
super super guay se le dan mil vueltas a
the possessed of the balls ok
los posesos de los huevos vale
but it doesn't attract me
pero a mí no me atrae
listen one day I see that each
oye que algún día veo que se venden cada
one sells for three thousand euros well I'll
una por tres mil euros pues ya me lo
think about it but I don't think so
pienso pero no creo
no I didn't I didn't have a video of pot in
no me no me había un vídeo de pot en
kill very good talking about its failure I
kill muy buena hablando de su fracaso lo
know  I know very good very good yes I know no I don't know
sé lo sé muy bueno muy bueno sí lo sé
but well we'll see the Comanche
pero bueno veremos a ver el comanche
also has NFC it's today whoever likes it can
también tiene nfc es hoy al que le guste
enjoy it the Comanche is given by the
que los disfruten el comanche la da por
FT also
los el ft también
also many people who like it have
también mucha gente que le gusta tiene
cake they like to invest in the stock market you know
pastel les gusta invertir en bolsa sabes
they like to try well I think that that's
les gusta probar pues yo creo que eso es
like a market
como un mercado
you know I suppose it's the feeling of
sabes supongo que es la sensación de
damn I bought something for 100 dollars and I
[__] compre algo por 100 dólares y lo
sold it for 3000 it's that feeling of saying it's
vendí por 3000 es esa sensación de decir
still like a game a little
no deja de ser como un juego un poco
good if you look at it that way
bueno si lo miras de esa forma pues
well you can understand it
bueno puedes entenderlo
but it's no longer like a game to say
pero deja de ser como un juego decir
always look something for 300 dollars and I
mira siempre algo por 300 dólares y lo
just sold it for 1500 pop you don't
acabo de vender por 1500 pop no te
feel good not because of the business power that you've
sientes bien no por el poder negocio que
made I
has hecho
think it's like a game
yo creo que es como como un juego
too in part
también en parte
but I've never been into
pero yo como nunca ha sido de
investments and I'm not one to give an
inversiones y eso tampoco soy nadie para
opinion because I have no idea about those
opinar porque no tengo ni idea de esas
things I don't
cosas
have any seeds
no tengo ni pipas
like a new challenge exactly and I see it
como un nuevo desafío exacto y yo lo veo
that way
de esa manera
for people who buy something for 1000 and
para la gente que compre algo por 1000 y
today it's worth a million  son of a [ __ ]
a día de hoy vale un millón hijo de [__]
how did you do it as a cs challenge it
como lo hiciste como un desafío cs
could look like this
podría verse así
well I don't look at my idea I don't know if
bueno yo no mira mi idea no sé si aquí
one ends here but well what I am
termina uno pero bueno lo que soy yo por
here my idea is
aquí mi idea es
the subject of the writing is worth the subject of the
el tema de la escrito vale el tema del
writing for me is to
escrito para mí es
leave it there forgotten like I
dejarlo ahí olvidado en plan yo lo
bought it at the beginning of last year and
compré a principios del año pasado y
leave it forgotten for one or two more years like that it's
dejarlo olvidado pues uno o dos años más
a crazy amount
en plan que que sea una burrada
we compare what investing is worth in fact I
comparamos lo que invertir vale de hecho
invested it well it seems like
lo invertí bueno ya me parece
investing to me in fact I hope that
invertir de hecho espero que se ha
the [ __ ] crazy amount that I have has been erased and
borrado la [__] burrada que tenga que y
that's there saved to bore me to
eso ahí guardado para aburrirme
bore me you know
para aburrirme me entiende
when such well I will sell it and of course from
cuando tal pues lo venderé y claro por
what I understand I'm
lo que tengo entendido
not going to tell you which one I bought
no os voy a decir cuál he comprado yo
because I don't want anyone to consider it
porque no quiero que nadie lo considere
as a recommendation or anything
como una recomendación ni nada por el
like that you know
estilo me entiende
now it goes more or less for the things for
ahora va más o menos por las cosas por
the crystals that I have put you know
los cristales que he puesto se sabe
but but of course I understand that when you
pero pero claro tengo entendido que eso
sell it not the day I
cuando lo cuando lo vendes no el día que
sell it I have to I have to
lo venda tengo que
pay the treasury 20 not
que pagar la hacienda 20 no
20 percent of what you have to
un 20 por ciento de las que tú tienes
pay making 20 percent of
que pagarle haciendo un 20 por ciento de
the profit of course
la ganancia claro
in  1921
en 1921
something out there what it is what is
algo por ahí lo que es lo que es el
Lebanon I think no I don't know I don't know
líbano creo que no no lo sé no sé
exactly pretend to enter I don't
exactamente pretender entrar
know I don't know
no sé no sé
to me in 13 on time there they are the expensive
a mí en 13 a tiempo allá son la cara
theory of Paula
teoría de paula
if they don't sell it no if they sell it
si no lo venden no si lo vende
haciendas would always be your cuts it's that
haciendas siempre sería tus tajadas es
touching your balls that they have to
que tocarte los huevos que se tengan que
take a cut of that is or rather that I
llevar tajada de eso es o sea que yo
make an investment
haga una inversión
and you earn money for an investment and they
y ganes dinero por una inversión y
also like money from that as if
también le agrada dinero de eso como si
they had invested like this
hubieran invertido ellos como esta
[ __ ] go to hell but that's how
[__] vete a la [__] [__] pero así
Spain is like that Spain in Andorra not in
españa así españa en andorra no en
Andorra writer
andorra escritor
how shameless but well finally
qué poca vergüenza pero bueno por fin
stopped because if he has to pay him
detuvo pues si le tiene que pagar a
feel like twenty something of what you
sienta un veintitantos de lo que de lo
earn well a percentage that you
que ganes pues un porcentaje que le
lose from the investment imagine that
pierdes a la inversión imagínate que
the entire investment has taken 40
toda la inversión le ha sacado un 40 por
percent well subtract a percentage that he
ciento pues restarle un porcentaje que
takes doing it is as I say
se lo lleva haciendo es como digo
then you know
entonces sabes
pass the fight he doesn't know anything about anything
pasa la contienda no sabe nada de nada
look listen to me I'll tell you one thing I don't care about
ya mira escúchame te digo una cosa yo
strange stories of rolls and such
paso de historias raras de rollos y de
then you understand  It's doing
entonces me entiende es haciendo las
things right and every now and then Fidel
cosas bien y de vez en cuando fidel
crashes not a bird read a fine I don't know
chocas no un ave leyó una multa no sé
what and I know a lot of colleagues those so
qué y conozco muchos compañeros los que
many with balls there are because you're
tantos con los [__] hay porque estás
wrong I turn I know that I touch wood it's
equivocada giro sé que yo toco madera
never worth it but I prefer to sleep
que nunca vale pero yo prefiero dormir
peacefully and look at where I live it's like that it's like that you
tranquilo y mirar hacia donde vivo es
understand me you have to
me entiendes
take half of what I
que me tienes que quitar la mitad de lo
earn they take half of what they have to
que gano me quitan la mitad que me tiene
take from me when I sell the writing they will
que quitar de la cuando venda el escrito
take a large part of the plot but it did
me quitarán gran parte de la trama pero
n't go beyond making strange moves that you never
no pasó de hacer movidas raras que nunca
do strange things shots things get expensive
hagáis cosas raras tiros las cosas salen
long
caras largas
you get what's due to you what's
tienes lo que te corresponde lo que te
due to you don't like from another country
corresponde no te gusta de otro país
the truth
la verdad
from here to when the sacks will be
de aquí a que los saques estarán
filling Rita grandfather already out of
llenando rita abuelo ya por
regret out of anger in Spain I would have
arrepentimiento por cabreo en españa yo
left I needed to be in Andorra I have
me hubiera ido requería estar en andorra
said it many times I would be in
lo he dicho muchas veces yo estaría en
two rappers to be and Andorra
dos raperos estar y andorra
of shooting I would have been giving realities
de tiro hubiera estaría dando realidades
in a year or two but
en un año o dos pero
I'm not going to leave because I have my children
no me voy a ir porque tengo mis hijos
here auto mission I don't have my family
aquí auto misión no tengo mi familia
set up here set up as if it were a
montada aquí montada como si fuera una
company my family has its roots my
empresa mi familia tiene sus raíces mi
family is here  Life is made
familia está aquí la vida tienen hecho
here, okay, I know, here it is, this is what
aquí vale yo sé aquí está esto es lo que
there is, I live well, I don't live badly, what
hay vivo bien no vivo mal
this is what needs to be done,
lo que esto es lo que hay que hacer
throw out the government of the country to
echar al gobierno del país a
revolutionize and have influencers and
revolucionarse y que haya influencer y
people who pepsi nonsense like the one he
gente que pepsi tonterías como la que
said and danced about, I don't care if they
decía y bailó de me da igual que me
take half of me because I have a lot to
quiten la mitad porque tengo mucho que
claim that things cannot be
reivindiquen que las cosas no pueden
said that there is no
decir que no hay ninguna explicación
logical explanation for those taxes that there are
lógica para esos impuestos que hay
ok
ok
[Music]
[Música]